A Guide to the Institute of International Education records, Publications, Paper records, RG 3, Series 1 FA1291
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Academic Mobility in a Changing World, Edited by Peggy Blumenthal, et al. (Higher Education Policy Series 29), 1996; 2 Copies (Box 18)
- North-South Scholarly Exchange: Access, Equity and Collaboration, Edited by Glenn L. Shive, et al., 1988 (Box 18)
- Missing the Boat: The Failure to Internationalize American Higher Education, Crauford D. Goodwin and Michael Nacht, 1991 (Box 18)
- Institute of International Education, News Bulletins Vol. 14.5 - 36.9, 1939-1961; Individual Bulletins, Soft Cover. (Box 19)
- Institute of International Education, News Bulletins Vol. 29-36, 1953-1961; Bound Volumes, Hard Cover. (Box 20)
- The Institute of International Education Annual Reports - 2nd series - 33rd series, 1921-1953; Series 4, 5, 6, 7 are not included. Some Reports are brittle and damaged. (Box 21)
- Institute of International Education, Annual Reports, 1938-1946; Some reports and brittle and damaged. (Box 21)
- Institute of International Education, Annual Reports, 1947-1953; Some reports and brittle and damaged. (Box 21)
- Institute of International Education, News Bulletins, Vol. VI, 1930 - 1931; Bound volumes, 2 copies. (Box 22)
- Institute of International Education, News Bulletins, Vol. VII, 1931-1932; Bound volumes, 2 copies. (Box 22)
- Institute of International Education, News Bulletins, Vol. VIII, 1932-1933; Bound volumes, 2 copies. (Box 22)
- Institute of International Education, News Bulletins, Vol. IX, 1933-1934; Bound volume (Box 22)
- Institute of International Education, News Bulletins, Vol. X, 1934-1935; Bound volumes, 2 copies. (Box 22)
- Institute of International Education, News Bulletins, Vol. XI, 1935-1936; Bound volumes, 2 copies. (Box 22)
- Institute of International Education, News Bulletins, Vol. XII, 1936-1937; Bound volumes, 2 copies. (Box 22)
- Institute of International Education, News Bulletins, Vol. XIII, 1937-1938; Bound volumes, 2 copies. (Box 22)
- Institute of International Education, News Bulletins, Vol. XIV, 1938=1939; Bound volumes, 2 copies. (Box 22)
- Institute of International Education, News Bulletins, Vol. XV, 1939-1940; Bound volumes, 2 copies. (Box 22)
- A Professor At Large, Stephen Duggan, 1945 (Box 24)
- In Search of Light: The Broadcasts of Edward R. Murrow, 1938-1961, 1967 (Box 24)
- The Rescue of Science and Learning: The Story of the Emergency Committee In Aid of Displaced Foreign Scholars, Stephen Duggan and Betty Drury, 1948 (Box 24)
- International Relations Clubs, Syllabus nos. I-XIV, 1920-1923 (Box 24)
- The Two Americas: An Interpretation, Stephen Duggan, 1934 (Box 24)
- A Student's Textbook in the History of Education, Revised Edition, Stephen Duggan, 1927 (Box 24)
- American Field Service Fellowships for French Universities, 1921-1923 (Box 24)
- Conference Between IIE and IEP, 1950 March 5 (Box 24)
- The Foreign Student: Exchangee or Immigrant - A Discussion of the Foreign Student Who Takes Up Permanent Residence in the United States (Committee on Educational Interchange Policy), 1958 May (Box 24)
- Increasing Women's Participation in International Scholarship Programs, Rona Kluga, 1996 (Box 25)
- A Foreign Student Guide to Chicago, Karen Bove and Linda Hillman, 1984, 1985 (Box 25)
- Study Abroad: You Can Get There from Here, 1995; 2 copies (Box 25)
- American Council on Education - Annual Meeting, 1979 October 31-November 2 (Box 25)
- Returning to Mexico - The Mexico Employment Guide for 1993-1994 Graduates of U.S. and Canadian Universities (Box 25)
- Returning to Hong Kong - The Hong Kong Employment Guide for Graduates of Overseas Universities (Box 25)
- Returning to Indonesia - The 2003-2004 Career Guide for Indonesian Graduates of American Universities, 2 copies (Box 25)
- Returning to Central Europe - 1999 Career Guide for Central European Students (Box 25)
- IIE Publications, 2009-2010 Editions, 2 copies (Box 25)
- Best Practices in Internalizing the Campus (IIE 2012 Best Practices Conference, New York City, 2012 March 9) (Box 25)
- Best Practices in Internalizing the Campus (IIE 2013 Best Practices Conference, New York City, 2013 March 22) (Box 25)
- Best Practices in Internalizing the Campus (IIE 2011 Best Practices Conference, New York City, 2011 March 18) (Box 25)
- Best Practices in Internalizing the Campus (IIE 2010 Best Practices Conference, New York City, 2010 March 19) (Box 25)
- Open Minds to the World - IIE 85 Years, 2004 (Box 25)
- Fulbright US Student Program, 2001-2002 (Box 25)
- Impact: Opening Minds to the World (Box 25)
- IIE Networker - International Education in Europe, 2010 Fall; 2 copies (Box 25)
- IIE Networker - International Education in Asia, 2010 Spring; 2 copies (Box 25)
- IIE Passport: Study Abroad in China, 2011; 2 copies (Box 25)
- Reaching Partners in Education, 2000 Fall; 2 copies (Box 25)
- Living Costs, Tuition and Fee Charges and Monthly Maintenance Allowance at American Universities, 1974-1986 (Box 25)
- Costs at U.S. Educational Institutions, 1984-1985; 2 copies (Box 25)
- Costs at U.S. Educational Institutions, 1985-1986; 2 copies (Box 25)
- The U.S. Independent Sector as it relates to South African Initiatives: A Directory, Ann McKinstry Micou, 1993 June; 2 copies (Box 25)
- The Donor Community in South Africa: A Directory, Ann McKinstry Micou, 1993 July; 2 copies (Box 25)
- Foreign Assistance to South Africa: A Directory, Ann McKinstry Micou, 1994 March; 2 copies (Box 25)
- Linkages at the Tertiary Level Between U.S. and South African Institutions, Ann McKinstry Micou, 1994 December; 2 copies (Box 25)
- IIE Passport: Academic Year Abroad, 38th edition, 2009-2010; 2 copies (Box 25)
- The Fulbright Experience (U.S. Department of State Brochure), 2 copies (Box 25)
- Expanding Study Abroad Capacity at U.S. Colleges and Universities, 2009 May (Box 25)
- Study Down Under - Magazine for Studying in Australia, 2004 (Box 25)
- Codes for Educational and Cultural Exchange (Department of State, Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs), 1975 June (Box 25)
- Brochures about IIE (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Teaching Abroad, 1973-1988 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Artists, 1969-1988 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Research in International Education, 1963-1969 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Opening Minds - Opening Doors, 1969-1996 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Guides, Handbooks and Studies for Foreign Students, 1960-1999 (Box 27, Folder 1-4)
- American Field Services, 1969-1986 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Report on Conferences, 1946-1973 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Special Annual Reports, 1964-1974 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Other Brochures (Study Abroad, College, etc.), 1970s-1990s (Box 27, Folder 8)
- IIE Membership Directory, 2008; 2 copies (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Meeting America's Global Education Challenge (IIE Study Abroad White Papers Series), Issues 1-6, 2007-2009 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Opening Minds to the World (IIE 85 Years), 2 copies (Box 28, Folder 3)
- IIE Educational Associates, 1988-1993 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- East Central Europe Information Exchange Report No. 2: Where Walls Once Stood - U.S. Responses to New Opportunities for Academic Cooperation with East Central Europe, Mary E. Kirk, 1992; 2 copies (Box 28, Folder 5)
- North American Higher Education Cooperation: An Inventory of U.S.-Canada and U.S.-Mexico Academic Linkages, 1993 September; 2 copies (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Raising the Curtain - A Report with Recommendations on Academic Exchanges with East Central Europe and the USSR, Barbara B. Burn (East Central Europe Information Exchange Report 1), 1991; 2 copies (Box 28, Folder 7)
- U.S. Advisory Commission on Public Diplomacy, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- International Exchange Locator, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Portraits of Small Business from the Developing World - Cases for Management Education, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Portraits of Business Practices in Emerging Markets - Cases for Management Education, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Current Status of Academic and Cultural Exchange Between US and People's Republic of China Institutions A Year After Tiananmen, 1990 November (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Reaching Partners in Education, 1999-2000; 2 copies (Box 28, Folder 13)
- IIE 1919-1989 (70th Anniversary) (Box 28, Folder 14)
- International Careers: Selected Resources, 1994 September (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Working Toward a New South Africa: IBM's Continuing Corporate Social Responsibility Programs (Box 29)
- Profiting from Education (Cover in Japanese), 1990 (Box 29)
- ITT International Fellowship Program, 1986-1987 (Box 29)
- Investing in Human Capital: Leadership for the Challenges of the 21st Century (IIE 75th Anniversary Forum), 1994; 2 copies (Box 29)
- The North American Consortium for Free Market Study: A Program for Central European Business and Economics Education, 1990 September (Box 29)
- The Role of Voluntary Organizations in Emerging Democracies: Experience and Strategies in Eastern and Central Europe and in South Africa, 1993 (Box 29)
- Oregon Governor's Commission on Foreign Language and International Studies - Final Report, 1982 August (Box 29)
- US-AEP Environmental Exchange Program, 1988 November (Box 29)
- Ripple in Still Water: Reflections by Activists on Local-and-National-Level Work on Economic, Social and Cultural Rights (International Human Rights Internship Program), 1997; 2 copies (Box 29)
- Education: A Global Commitment, International Education: A Global Resource (Box 29)
- To Strengthen the Nation's Investment in Foreign Languages and International Studies - A Legislative Proposal to Create a National Foundation for Foreign Languages and International Studies (Association of American Universities), 1986 October 1 (Box 29)
- Connect: Employee Self Service User Guide Version 4.1, 2007 (Box 29)
- Regional Education Profile: Asia (China, Hong Kong, Macau, Thailand, Indonesia, Malaysia, Brunei), 1986 March (Box 29)
- South African Information Exchange Working Papers, No. 29-30 (Box 29)
- Financial Status of Students/Scholars from the People's Republic of China on US Campuses, 1989-1990 (Box 29)
- Current Status of Academic and Cultural Exchange Between US and People's Republic of China Institutions A Year After Tiananmen, 1990 November (Box 29)
- Opportunities and Challenges in US-China Education Linkages: Reviewing the Past, Surveying the Present, Charting A Course for the Future, Shepherd Laughlin, 2008 June (Box 29)
- Looking to the Future: IIE's Mission in the Years Ahead, 1994 (Box 29)
- Educational Exchange Between the United States and China, 2008 (Box 29)
- Report to the Trustees of the Rotary Foundation: An Evaluation of the Rotary International Scholarship Program, 1992 January (Box 29)
- Doubling the Number of US Students in Europe: Exploring Models for Exchange, 2009 March 20 (Box 29)
- Education for Nambians: A Workshop Report, Lynne Loomis-Price (The Namibian Education Program Working Papers, No. 1), 1989 April (Box 29)
- Forward Together: The United States Role in Nambian Education and Training, Walter R. Johnson with David E. Devlin-Foltz (The Namibian Education Program Working Papers, No. 2), 1993 (Box 29)
- The Banyan Tree Paradox: Culture and Human Rights Activism (International Human Rights Internship Program), 2006 (Box 29)
- Circle of Rights - Economic, Social and Cultural Rights Activism: A Training Resource (International Human Rights Internship Program), 2000 (Box 29)
- European NGO's Providing Resources for Development and Social Justice in South Africa: A Handbook, Ann McKinstry Micou (South African Information Exchange Working Papers, No. 18), 1991 November (Box 29)
- IIE Passport: Study Abroad in China (Box 29)
- International India: A Turning Point in Educational Exchange with the U.S. (Global Education Research Reports, Report Three), 2010 (Box 29)
- US Background Preparations and Policy Formulation for the United Nations Conference on Science and Technology for Development, 1979 August (Box 29)
- Recruitment Guide for Thailand, 1998 (Box 29)
- The University in Society: An Inter-American Dialogue, 1974; 2 copies (Box 29)
- World Directory of Environmental Education Programs, 1973 (Box 29)
- US Advisory Commission on Public Diplomacy, 2002 (Box 29)
- Profiting from Education (in Japanese), 3 copies (Box 29)
- Fulbright and other grants for graduate study abroad, 1990-1991 (Box 30)
- U.S. Student Fulbright Grants and Other Grants for Graduate Study and Research Abroad, 1994-1995 (Box 30)
- Fulbright and Other Grants for Graduate Study Abroad, 1989-1990 (Box 30)
- U.S. Fulbright Fellows - Directory of Students, 1993-1994, 1994-1995 (Box 30)
- U.S. Fulbright Fellows - Directory of Grantees, 1991-1992, 1992-1993 (Box 30)
- Academic Year Abroad, 1986-1987; 2 Copies (Box 30)
- Academic Year Abroad, 1989-1990; 2 Copies (Box 30)
- Academic Year Abroad, 1990-1991; 2 Copies (Box 30)
- Academic Year Abroad, 1991-1992; 2 Copies (Box 30)
- Academic Year Abroad, 1992-1993; 2 Copies (Box 30)
- Financial Resources for International Study: A Guide for U.S. Students and Professionals (IIE), 1996; 2 copies (Box 31)
- Financial Resources for International Study: A Definitive Guide to Organizations Offering Awards for Overseas Study (Peterson's), 1989; 2 copies (Box 31)
- Open Doors: Report on International Educational Exchange, 1991-1994 (Box 31)
- Open Doors: Report on International Educational Exchange, 2004-2006 (Box 31)
- Profiles 1991-1992 - Detailed Analyses of the Foreign Student Population (Box 31)
- Continental Responsibility: European and International Support for Higher Education and Research in East Central Europe, Editors, Mary E. Kirk and Aaron A. Rhodes, 1994; 2 copies (Box 31)
- Fortifying the Foundations: US Support for Developing and Strengthening Democracy in East Central Europe, Editor, Mark Lazar, 1996; 2 copies (Box 31)
- Open Doors: Report on International Educational Exchange, 2005; Digital media, CD-ROM (Box 31)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. Access copy is currently available. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
- Short-Term Training, 2001; Digital media, CD-ROM, 2 copies (Box 31)
- IIE Passport: Study Abroad Funding - A Guide for U.S. Students and Professionals, 2007; Digital, CD-ROM, 2 copies (Box 31)
- Global Education Research Reports, No. 1-4, 2008-2010; 2 copies each (Box 31)
- Funding for U.S. Study: A Guide for Foreign Nationals, 1992; 2 copies (Box 32)
- Funding for United States Study: A Guide for International Students and Professionals, 1996, 2007-2011 (Box 32)
- IIE Network Membership Directory, 2005-2007, 2009-2010 (Box 32)
- Joint and Double Degree Programs: An Emerging Model for Transatlantic Exchange, Editor, Daniel Obst and Matthias Kuder, 2009; 2 copies (Box 33)
- Higher Education in Africa: Equity, Access, Opportunity, Editor, Sabine O'Hara (Africa Higher Education Collaborative, AHEC), 2010; 2 copies (Box 33)
- Intensive English USA: The World's Most Complete Guide to English Language Instruction, 2000, 2005, 2006, 2010; includes CD-ROM (Box 33)
- English Language and Orientation Programs in the United States, 1969-1991; 2 copies each/ 8 volumes (Box 33)
- Foreign Students in Community, Junior and Technical College, 1979; 2 copies (Box 33)
- Study America (partially in Japanese), 2008; 2 copies (Box 33)
- Impact, 2 copies (Box 33)
- Returning to Brazil: The Brazilian Employment Guide for Graduates of U.S. Universities, 2001; 2 copies (Box 33)
- Bilingual and International Schools in Mexico and Central America, 2005; 2 copies (Box 33)
- Bilingual Schools in Mexico, 2002; 2 copies (Box 33)
- Spanish Study in Mexico, 1997-1998, 2004 (Box 33)
- Academic Year Abroad - The Most Complete Guide to Planning Academic Year Study Abroard, 1987-1988, 1988-1989, 1994-1995, 1999-2000, 2000-2001; 2 copies each except 1987-1988 (Box 34)
- Academic Year Abroad - The Most Complete Guide to Planning Academic Year Study Abroard, 2001-2003; 2 copies each (Box 35)
- IIE Passport: Academic Year Abroad - The Most Complete Guide to Planning Academic Year Abroad, 2005; 2 copies (Box 35)
- IIE Passport: Academic Year Abroad - The Most Complete Guide to Planning Academic Year Abroad, 2006-2010; 2 copies each (Box 36)
- IIE Passport: Short-Term Study Abroad, 2005, 2007-2010 (Box 36)
- Management Study Abroad, 1989-1991 (Box 37)
- IIE Passport: Study Abroad in the Americas, 2010; 2 copies (Box 37)
- IIE Passport: Study Abroad in Asia and Oceania, 2010; 2 copies (Box 37)
- IIE Passport: Study Abroad in Africa and the Middle East, 2010; 2 copies (Box 37)
- IIE Passport: Study Abroad in Europe, 2010; 2 copies (Box 37)
- Study Abroad Pamphlets, 1970s-1990s (Box 37)
- Needs of Foreign Students from Developing Nations at U.S. Colleges and Universities (Box 37)
- Communications Technology and the Crisis in Education: A Report on the Bahia Workshop, Council on Higher Education in the American Republics (CHEAR), 1971; 2 copies (Box 37)
- An International Student's Guide to Mexican Universities, 1995 (Box 37)
- The Journal of Asian Studies, 2001 May (Box 37)
- Foreign Languages - Human Capital Approach Needed to Correct Staffing and Proficiency Shortfalls, 2002 January (Box 37)
- World Forum of Ideas and Actions, New York Meeting, IIE, 809 United States Plaza, 1992 June 5-7 (Box 37)
- IIE?Now, 1976 (Box 37)
- Funding for United States Study: A Scholarship Guide for Europeans, 2005; 2 copies (Box 37)
- Funding U.S. Studies: Graduate and Post-Graduate Opportunities for Latin Americans, 2003 (Box 37)
- Returning to Hong Kong: The Hong Kong Employment Guide for 1990 Graduates of Overseas Universities (The American Chamber of Commerce in Hong Kong) (Box 38)
- US College-Sponsored Programs Abroad: Academic Year (The Learning Traveler), 1982 (Box 38)
- Student Mobility and the Internationalization of Higher Education: National Policies and Strategies from Six World Regions, 2011 (Box 38)
- Study in the United Kingdom and Ireland: The Most Completed Guide to the Most Popular Destination for Study Abroad, 1987-1988, 1988-1989 (Box 38)
- Higher Education Reform: Implications for Foreign Students, Editor, Barbara B. Burn, 1978 (Box 38)
- Summer Learning Options USA: A Guide for Foreign Nationals, 1983; 2 copies (Box 38)
- Atlas of Student Mobility, Todd M. Davis, 2003; 2 copies (Box 38)
- Vietnam Career Guide: A Career Guide for the New Millenium, 2001; 2 copies (Box 38)
- Japan-US Women Leaders Dialogue: Community Development and the Role of Women, 1994; 2 copies (Box 38)
- Recruitment Guide for Thailand, 1998 (Box 38)
- Returning to Thailand: The 2001-2002 Career Guide for Thai Graduates of American Universities, 2 copies (Box 38)
- Returning to South Africa: The 2000 Career Guide for South African Graduates of American Universities, 2002; 2 copies (Box 38)
- Returning to Russia: The 1998 Career Guide for Russian Graduates of American Universities, 2 copies (Box 38)
- Returning to Central Europe: 1999 Career Guide for Central European Students, 2 copies (Box 38)
- Planning for Study Abroad: Making it Meaningful and Manageable - Moving Image Video, 2017:002:001; 2 copies, Moving Image Video (Box 38)
  Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
- Specialized Study Options USA - A Guide to Short-Term Educational Programs in the United States for Foreign Nationals, Editor, Edrice Howard, 1986-1988 (Box 39)
- Bridges to Knowledge: Foreign Students in Comparative Perspective, Editor, Elinor G. Barber, Philip G. Altbach and Robert G. Myers, 1984; 2 copies (Box 39)
- Abroad and Beyond: Patterns in American Overseas Education, Craufurd D. Goodwin, Michael Nacht, 1988 (Box 39)
- Engaging the Arab and Islamic World through Public Diplomacy: A Report and Action Recommendations, Editor, William A. Rugh, 2004 (Box 39)
- Students from the Arab World and Iran (National Association for Foreign Student Affairs), 1978 (Box 39)
- Increasing Women's Participation in International Scholarship Programs: An Analysis of Nine Case Studies, Rona Kluger, 1996 (Box 39)
- Summer Programs in the U.S.: A Guide for Foreign Students, 1977; 2 copies (Box 39)
- Education Superior e Integracion Regional de America del Norte, 1993; 2 copies (Box 39)
- Higher Education in the 21st Century: Global Challenge and National Response, Editor, Philip G. Altbach and Patti McGill Peterson, 1999; 2 copies (Box 39)
- Kosovo: An Unfinished Peace, William G. O'Neill (International Peace Academy Occassional Paper Series), 2002 (Box 39)
- Creating a New Civilization: The Politics of the Third Wave, Alvin and Heidi Toffler, 1994 (Box 39)
- NGO Development Training in Southern Africa: Promoting South-South Linkages Through Information Sharing, Vol. 1., Ann McKinstry Micou (Southern African Information Exchange, Working Paper 29), 1995-1996 (Box 39)
- Guide to Regional Networking in Southern Africa: Cross-Border Linkages to Promote Democracy and Development, Ann McKinstry Micou (Southern African Information Exchange, Working Paper 32), 1996 December; 2 copies (Box 39)
- Succeeding as an international Student in the U.S. and Canada, Charles Lipson, 2008 (Box 40)
- Russia - How to Develop Partnerships Between U.S. and Russian Universities: From Motivation to Results (U.S.-Russia Social Expertise Exchange Higher Education Working Group), 2015; 2 copies (Box 40)
- Improving Health Policy in Africa, 2004 (Box 40)
- The Rescue of Science and Learning (IIE Scholar Research Fund), 2012; 2 copies (Box 40)
- Funding For Latin Americas to Study and Research in the U.S., 2001; 2 copies (Box 40)
- Best Practices in Internationalizing the Campus, Intistute of International Education, New York City, 2010 March 19; 2 copies (Box 40)
- Open Doors, Report on International Educational Exchange, 2015; 2 copies (Box 40)
- IIE Networker, 2014 Fall; 2 copies (Box 40)
- Latin America's New Knowledge Economy: Higher Education, Government and International Cooperation, Editor, Jorge Balan (Global Education Research Reports, Report Seven), 2013; 2 copies (Box 40)
- Expanding U.S Study Abroad to Turkey: A Guide for Institutions, Report prepared by Patricia Chow and Kimberly Cho (IIE White Papers Series, Issue 9), 2011 August; 2 copies (Box 40)
- The Boren Awards: A Report of Oral Language Proficiency Gains during Academic Study Abroad, Lee Mason, Christopher Powers and Seamus Donnelly, 2015 September (Box 40)
- Expanding U.S. Study Abroad to Indonesia: U.S. and Indonesian Perspectives and Strategies for Expansion, Report prepared by Clare Banks and Shannon Harrison (IIE White Paper Series, Issue 10), 2011 (Box 40)
- Expanding U.S Study Abroad to Brazil: A Guide for Institutions, Patricia Chow and Charles Gale, 2012 May; 2 copies (Box 40)
- IIE Victor J. Goldberg Prize for Peace in the Middle East, 2015; 2 copies (Box 41)
- Asia: The Next Higher Education Superpower (Global Education Research Reports, Report 9), Edited by Rajika Bhandari and Alessia Lefebure, 2015 (Box 41)
- A Parent Guide to Study Abroad, 2015; 2nd copy in Spanish (Box 41)
- IIE Network Handbook for International Educators, 2016 (Box 41)
- Intensive English USA: IIE's Comprehensive Guide to English Language Instruction in the United States, 2016; 2 copies (Box 41)
- Funding for United States Study: A Guide for International Students and Professionals, 2017; 2 copies (Box 41)
- Open Doors: Report on International Educational Exchange, 2008; Digital, CD-ROM (Box 41)
- Open Doors: Report on International Educational Exchange, 2013 (Box 41)
- Open Doors: Report on International Educational Exchange, 2014 (Box 41)
- IIE Networker - Virtual Exchange: Connected Learning in the Digital Age, 2016 Fall; 2 copies (Box 41)
- IIE Passport 2014-2015: A Complete Guide to Study Abroad Programs, 2014 April (Box 41)